sideshow.com 2019-10-12

# Privacy Policy | Sideshow Collectibles

_Effective date: May 25th, 2018_

Sideshow Inc. (“us”, “we”, or “our”) operates the https://www.sideshow.com website (the “Website”).

This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of personal data when you use our Service and the choices you have associated with that data. This privacy policy applies to any Sideshow Inc. website, application, service, or tool (individually “Service” and collectively “Services”) where this privacy policy is referenced, regardless of how you access or use them, including through mobile devices.

We use your data to provide and improve the Services. This Privacy Policy is solely intended to inform you of our data collection practices and your rights to any of your data that we may collect. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, accessible from [https://www.sideshow.com](https://www.sideshow.com/terms/ "Terms and Conditions").

### Definitions

**Personal Data**  
Personal Data means information relating to an identified or identifiable individual. An identifiable individual is one who can be identified, directly or indirectly, by reference to an identifier such as a name, a device identification number, location data, an online identifier, or to one or more factors specific to the physical, physiological, genetic, mental, economic, cultural or social identity of that natural person.

**Usage Data**  
Usage Data is data collected automatically either generated by the use of the Service or from the Service infrastructure itself (for example, the duration of a page visit).

**Cookies**  
Cookies are small pieces of data stored on a User’s device.

**Data Controller and Data Protection Officer**  
Data Controller means a person who (either alone or jointly or in common with other persons) determines the purposes for which and the manner in which any personal data are, or are to be, processed.

For the purpose of this Privacy Policy, we are a Data Controller of your data.

Where we have a legal obligation to do so, we have appointed data protection officers (DPOs) to be responsible for our privacy program. You can contact our DPO via the Contact Us information detailed below in this privacy policy.

**Data Processor (or Service Providers)**  
Data Processor (or Service Provider) means any person (other than an employee of the Data Controller) who processes the data on behalf of the Data Controller.  
We may use the services of various Service Providers in order to process your data more effectively.

**Data Subject**  
Data Subject is any living individual who is the subject of Personal Data.

**User**  
The User is the individual using our Service. The User corresponds to the Data Subject, who is the subject of Personal Data.

### Information Collection And Use

We collect different types of information for various purposes to provide and improve our Service to you.

**Types of Data Collected**

**_Personal Data_**  
While using our Services, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you (“Personal Data”). Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to:

  * Email address
  * First name and last name
  * Phone number
  * Address, State, Province, ZIP/Postal code, City
  * Cookies and Usage Data

We may use your Personal Data to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to you. You may opt in to receiving any, or all, of these communications from us by following the subscribe link or instructions provided in any email we send.

**_Usage Data_**  
We may also collect information concerning your access and use of the Services (“Usage Data”). This Usage Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol address (e.g. IP address), browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data.

**_Location Data_**  
We may use and store information about your location if you give us permission to do so (“Location Data”). We use this data to provide features of our Service, to improve and customize our Service.

You can enable or disable location services when you use our Service at any time, through your device settings.

**_Tracking Cookies Data_**  
We use cookies and similar tracking technologies to track the activity on our Service and hold certain information.  
Cookies are files with small amount of data which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored on your device. Tracking technologies also used are beacons, tags, and scripts to collect and track information and to improve and analyze our Service.

You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Service.

Examples of Cookies we use:

  * **Session Cookies.** We use Session Cookies to operate our Service.
  * **Preference Cookies.** We use Preference Cookies to remember your preferences and various settings.
  * **Security Cookies.** We use Security Cookies for security purposes.

**Use of Data**

We use your personal information to fulfill a contract with you and provide you with our Services, to comply with our legal obligation, protect your vital interest, or as may be required for the public good. This includes:

  * To provide and maintain our Services
  * To notify you about changes to our Services
  * To allow you to participate in interactive features of our Services when you choose to do so
  * To provide customer support
  * To prevent, detect, mitigate, and investigate fraud, security breaches or other potentially prohibited or illegal activities

We also use your personal information to pursue our legitimate interests where your rights and freedoms do not outweigh these interests. We have implemented controls to balance our interests with your rights. This includes to:

  * gather analysis or valuable information so that we can improve our Service
  * monitor the usage of our Service
  * detect, prevent and address technical issues

With your consent, we may use your personal information to:

  * provide you with news, special offers and general information about other goods, services and events which we offer that are similar to those that you have already purchased or enquired about unless you have opted not to receive such information
  * Provide you with marketing from third parties
  * Customize third party advertising you might see on third party websites

You have the right to withdraw your consent at any time.

**Retention of Data**

Sideshow Inc. will retain your Personal Data only for as long as is necessary for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. We will retain and use your Personal Data to the extent necessary to comply with our legal obligations (for example, if we are required to retain your data to comply with applicable laws), resolve disputes, and enforce our legal agreements and policies.

Sideshow Inc. will also retain Usage Data for internal analysis purposes. Usage Data is generally retained for a shorter period of time, except when this data is used to strengthen the security or to improve the functionality of our Services, or we are legally obligated to retain this data for longer time periods.

**Transfer Of Data**

Your information, including Personal Data, may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than those from your jurisdiction.

If you are located outside United States and choose to provide information to us, please note that we transfer the data, including Personal Data, to United States and process it there.

Sideshow Inc. will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy and no transfer of your Personal Data will take place to an organization or a country unless there are adequate controls in place including the security of your data and other personal information. The transfer of such data is typically for the purpose of fulfilling our contract with you, as specified above. Therefore, any request to delete or modify such Personal Data may result in the termination or interruption of our Services with respect to your usage of such Services.

**Disclosure Of Data**

**Disclosure for Law Enforcement**  
Under certain circumstances, Sideshow Inc. may be required to disclose your Personal Data if required to do so by law or in response to valid requests by public authorities (e.g. a court or a government agency).

**Legal Requirements**  
Sideshow Inc. may disclose your Personal Data in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:

  * To comply with a legal obligation
  * To protect and defend the rights or property of Sideshow Inc.
  * To prevent or investigate possible wrongdoing in connection with the Service
  * To protect the personal safety of users of the Service or the public
  * To protect against legal liability

**Change of Control**  
If we are subject to a merger or acquisition with/by another company, we may share information with them in accordance with our privacy standards. Should such an event occur, we will require that the new combined entity follow this privacy policy with respect to your Personal Data. If we intend to handle your Personal Data for any purposes not covered in this privacy notice, you will receive prior notification of the processing of your Personal Data for the new purposes.

**Security Of Data**  
We protect your Personal Data using technical and administrative security measures to reduce the risks of loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure and alteration. Some of the safeguards we use may include firewalls and data encryption, physical access controls to our data centers, and information access authorization controls. The security of your Personal Data is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Data, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

### “Do Not Track” Signals

We do not support Do Not Track (“DNT”). Do Not Track is a preference you can set in your web browser to inform websites that you do not want to be tracked.  
You can enable or disable Do Not Track by visiting the Preferences or Settings page of your web browser.

### Your Rights

Sideshow Inc. aims to take reasonable steps to allow you to correct, amend, delete, or limit the use of your Personal Data.

Whenever made possible, you can update your Personal Data directly within your account settings section. If you are unable to change your Personal Data, please contact us to make the required changes.

If you wish to be informed what Personal Data we hold about you and if you want it to be removed from our systems, please contact us.

You have the right:

  * to know what personal information we maintain about you
  * to receive a copy of your personal information in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable or commonly used electronic format on request
  * To update and modify personal information is incorrect or incomplete
  * to object to our processing of your personal information when collection is based on a legitimate interest
  * to delete or restrict how we use your personal information, but this right is determined by applicable law and may impact your access to some of our Services

Please note that we may ask you to verify your identity before responding to such requests.

### Service Providers

Sideshow may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Services (“Service Providers”), to provide the Services on our behalf, to perform Service-related services or to assist us in analyzing how our Services are used.

Sideshow may collect your email address via cookies and pixels on the Website through the use of trusted third party partners. These partners may combine your email information with other information they have access to such as mailing address so that we may serve relevant marketing offers to you via direct mail. If you do not want us to collect information about you, please refer to the ‘contact us’ area below.

These third parties have access to your Personal Data only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.

### Analytics

We may use third-party Service Providers to monitor and analyze the use of our Service.

  * **Google Analytics**  
Google Analytics is a web analytics service offered by Google that tracks and reports website traffic. Google uses the data collected to track and monitor the use of our Service. This data is shared with other Google services. Google may use the collected data to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.  
You can opt-out of having made your activity on the Service available to Google Analytics by installing the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on. The add-on prevents the Google Analytics JavaScript (ga.js, analytics.js, and dc.js) from sharing information with Google Analytics about visits activity.  
For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy Terms web page: http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/

### Behavioral Remarketing

Sideshow Inc. uses remarketing services to advertise on third party websites to you after you visited our Services. We and our third-party vendors use cookies to inform, optimize and serve ads based on your past visits to our Service. To the extent that any such collection or use of your Personal Data involves automated decision-making, we and our third parties have implemented appropriate safeguards to ensure your legal and personal rights are not affected. You have the right to access and review such safeguards, and opt in our opt out as may be required, through the links provided to our third-party vendor privacy policies and notices below.

  * **Google AdWords**  
Google AdWords remarketing service is provided by Google Inc.  
You can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize the Google Display Network ads by visiting the Google Ads Settings page: http://www.google.com/settings/ads  
Google also recommends installing the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on – https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout – for your web browser. Google Analytics  
Opt-out Browser Add-on provides visitors with the ability to prevent their data from being collected and used by Google Analytics.  
For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy Terms web page: http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/
  *   * **Twitter**  
Twitter remarketing service is provided by Twitter Inc.  
You can opt-out from Twitter’s interest-based ads by following their instructions: https://support.twitter.com/articles/20170405  
You can learn more about the privacy practices and policies of Twitter by visiting their Privacy Policy page: https://twitter.com/privacy
  *   * **Pinterest**  
You can learn more about the privacy practices and policies of Pinterest by visiting their Privacy Policy page: https://policy.pinterest.com/en/privacy-policy
  *   * **Facebook**  
Facebook remarketing service is provided by Facebook Inc.  
You can learn more about interest-based advertising from Facebook by visiting this page: https://www.facebook.com/help/164968693837950  
To opt-out from Facebook’s interest-based ads follow these instructions from Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/help/568137493302217  
Facebook adheres to the Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising established by the Digital Advertising Alliance. You can also opt-out from Facebook and other participating companies through the Digital Advertising Alliance in the USA http://www.aboutads.info/choices/, the Digital Advertising Alliance of Canada in Canada http://youradchoices.ca/ or the European Interactive Digital Advertising Alliance in Europe http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/, or opt-out using your mobile device settings.  
For more information on the privacy practices of Facebook, please visit Facebook’s Data Policy: https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation
  * **4cite**  
More details can be found at: https://www.4cite.com/4cite-marketing-llc-privacy-policy/
  * **PhotoSlurp**  
More details can be found at: https://hi.photoslurp.com/privacy-policy/

### Payments

We may provide paid products and/or services within the Service. In that case, we use third-party services for payment processing (e.g. payment processors).  
We will not store or collect your payment card details. That information is provided directly to our third-party payment processors whose use of your personal information is governed by their Privacy Policy. These payment processors adhere to the standards set by PCI-DSS as managed by the PCI Security Standards Council, which is a joint effort of brands like Visa, Mastercard, American Express and Discover. PCI-DSS requirements help ensure the secure handling of payment information.

The payment processors we work with are:

  * **Reach**  
Their policies can be viewed at https://withreach.com/privacy-policy.html
  *   * **PayPal**  
Their policies can be viewed at https://www.paypal.com/us/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full

### Links To Other Sites

Our Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party’s site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.

We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.

### Children’s Privacy

Our Services are intended for a general audience and are not intended for children. We do not knowingly collect personal information from users deemed to be children under their respective national laws. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your child has provided us with Personal Data, please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected Personal Data from children without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information from our servers.

### Changes To This Privacy Policy

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.  
We will let you know via email and/or a prominent notice on our Service, prior to the change becoming effective and update the “effective date” at the top of this Privacy Policy.

You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.

### Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us:

  * Reach our Data Protection Officer by email: [support@sideshow.com](mailto:support@sideshow.com "Email Support")
  * By visiting this page on our website: <https://www.sideshow.com/contact/>
  * By phone number: 1-805-214-2100
